That look at this, there is also their thanks, there is
no light coming in the enthusiasm, this is a small thing with me
and any government secretary
turned out that till now there were
problems of Bajana Gaut all Thakur's
brother, so in today's video, the special
TVS Apache 160 will be involved in basic education,
looking back,
this is my wife,
if brother you have this bike, TVS
Apache 160 4V VS model or you are going to buy it, then
this video is also very sad for you, the
video has complete information
and long investment arrangements, I do
n't know even for 5 minutes, so many Yogi
videos will be useful for you, I will put them in a lot of videos
and do professorship in it, then
I will be against rape, if you are planning to buy a bike, then
I
would personally request that you buy Apache bike, it is going to be
around a year,
10 months ago, last year Mi2 and on 27th
May Rosamond Pike was purchased and Abhay is going to be
around a year in the second, and
in between this, the Mi Express is very
bad, I have put my  The videos are powerful, I told you first that
whatever I am telling about suicide is absolutely
true brother, there is no lie in it,
you are not there on 14th August, do not do it, there is no
problem in it, watch your video of physical, if you do
not feel like watching then do not
watch it, if you bring it, watch it in your informative
video, I have brought videos
that whatever is happening with me right now, whatever
problem you are stuck in, you should also tell your
child about it, that is why the
video I have made, today my mood is
very bad in the morning, the first problem is in my brother's
mind, then
what is the problem in it, the first
more thing in my brother is that he should once
again remain connected, the power jua is very hard, it is
white, there is no side effect
and this problem has got stuck later for the third or fourth
time, I came to him again this morning
and before this, I
took him to the service center, Sapla Aryan TV
center,
A P, the first two times when I had
problems, they did not help me, the first
time on that day or the second time, maybe it is the first
time, they did not do that at all  I
applied finely chopped repair tape etc.
after changing it, it would get rid of it, it
ran on the fifteenth day, 1972, if there is any problem then my
brother took it again, we will
replace it in the name of motors, I
subscribed here, there is
this and there is a problem,
so I told him that this is the problem with me, then
he said that there is a wire which is
attached with the vote and it is really good,
so they were connecting it in its place, I thought it is
okay, he is saying okay, then it is okay Babu,
brother, I have taken it, 15-20 days, one
month is left, you had
uploaded the video of the jodhpur service, I will send it for fourteen kilometers, I am
confident that there will be no problem in 600 kilometers,
maybe I don't remember the exact date, then
tell him that there will be a
problem at that time, if this
fee is increased then I should send Meghna, I said it is okay,
I took you, she did
not get me checked, she showed me the service,
she had done a good service, it was absolutely
smooth, so she was satisfied that we will
talk to you tomorrow, problem is fine  You will
get it, so this morning as I was
going to Delhi, I was going to pick it up, then
within a hundred meters the Jal Aayog picked up the
bike, then again it is
yours,
I took that big debit card of the cycle, I will
take it with me, it is the same
mechanical one, as soon as I opened it, I
found the bike for resting, I had
not kept the bike, I will get it entered
in New Jersey, Avatar was the same,
his shampoo was strong, it flew away, its
door is useless, then I have brought the
divider in this, that is
Ajay
and he is trapped in anti-social activities with me,
brother, it is getting switched off again and again, it is
22, it gets switched off while moving, many times it gets switched off,
mostly the bikes do not
stop, I apply brakes, if switched off then the
power gets cut automatically, hey, keep a lot of it in my hotel
among the other groups,
I told you, then the salwar will be available in the beginning, as
before, they also got a little push
with alum brother, nothing happened to me,
then I cried
If we are facing any problem in getting it back for service, then
they will
sit a little bit at the back and say that it has been
fixed, it did not come immediately, so as soon as
I got it serviced, then
my decision was to make a Vaishnav video, it is the
decoration of the house that I want to buy,
show it to them for service, brother, see friend, then do a
little bit of it, he
said that now it will be fine, if it comes
to doing it again, but Murasi means
only that process, so I have made this channel,
now do it later, Yadav,
for you, first of all, I will
show you what happened, so much so that Sunita
got her main Jyoti, the mic was getting shut down, there was
some problem in it,
it got completely fixed now, so that
Hero bike is at equal distance, I searched many of
my friends who are knowledgeable, who have
Apache bikes, the
problem of it getting shut down, so there are many of them,
I have seen videos of many, some even in the morning, I
mean somewhere, this problem is with all of them, but
still this problem is very much, let's go with the customer, that
you thought friend, that with me on social media  I had
made a video of the complaint that I want to take and I have
finally
sent an email for it today by measuring it,
proper screenshot, rules, listening to details
etc. and whatever the
headquarter of TVS is that you have sent the mail to, we will
see if some reply will come from them,
if there is no new time then the
test was over at the same place, it is against the service center
and see the procedure for it further
because now it is going on in the next month May
and its quantity will be
completed and after that whatever will be installed and you will
wear a turban, the warranty is over that no one will get
any tampering done with Bloody Mary,
this is a
complete site which we have ever done today Steve Jobs's online
customer care ad all TVS
Motors.com or their pair is a single site,
whatever problem you are having on this,
you can
email that soldier but I have
also made a proper video for 130 by matching it with them
in BJP, so whatever update they give,
whatever will be their reaction.  I
update the measurements and seventhly and that click
is fine, I will show you how the
power is cut brother, at the end of the video, if I
show you something new somewhere, you have seen it, then
I and that is the first time that we have
made a video with the face, it is
necessary, it is the first video and
in some express the driver had
said something in front of the camera, there is some addiction, anything that
means something wrong in the video, so
I ignored it please because my mood is
very bad and I was thinking that whatever
process I am doing
and it is difficult for you to lose the video
or you had to sell it to someone, that is why the
video that I
made was that
if you do not tell me
how to find a solution for what or what should I do,
where should I complain,
then whatever is the
problem with my bike with the back, it has been solved, then
you should definitely
suggest by commenting, friend, you are very
troubled by that, I took this mic and
you should take some care with this, this vegetable  All the
updates will be there if I give through my video, right now no
action notification has been done with my brother's mining, there is nothing to be done about it,
something is
visible about the cut made, such
notification has not been done in the style and now this
recently installed indicator is
absolutely ready, understand its power is
very less, that electricity bill is not much, that
someone has not even installed the indicator in his house,
some patients again nothing, so that is why
I am repeatedly asking for their
video, first I have
brought it to the service center, till then it is being seen, so
go to their place tomorrow, initially
talk to them and see what happened or not,
if you are buying this TVS Apache 160 4V tree model, then
he should know everything after
checking the parts properly and after checking them properly
and I mean, he will take advice from whoever has a
bike nearby which has been there for some time, that
means what is it promising, then at
that time you should make the purchase in the bag
and  Like me, when I had bought the bike, then just for
fun, I neither
asked anyone nor was told anything else in the showroom and
I left with the bike and this bike of mine was
decided to take one and a half part for sample testing, in the beginning
my friend bought the bike, she was also pregnant,
so in the interest of my show, I did
not pay much attention to everything
and purchased the bike by
phone, so you should not make this mistake, if you suffer a
loss of one and a half lakh rupees without any reason then it is a big deal.